National Organization for Women, New York State Chapter; Records apap029
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
National Organization for Women (NOW), New York State Chapter Records
1961-2011
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
National Organization for Women. New York Chapter
apap029
55.09 cubic ft.
The New York State chapter of NOW aims to bring women into full participation in the mainstream of American society in order to exercise all privileges and responsibilities in an equal partnership with men. Working close with the Senate, political candidates,other women organizations, and community activists, NOW-NYS members work to defend women from inequality.
Administrative History
The New York State Chapter of the National Organization for Women, the first state chapter to be chartered in the United States, was founded on February 6, 1967. The New York State Chapter has the same purpose as the National Organization: to bring women into full participation in the mainstream of American society in order to exercise all privileges and responsibilities in an equal partnership with men. This purpose includes equal rights and responsibilities in all aspects of citizenship, public service, employment, education, and family life, as well as freedom from discrimination because of age, marital status, sexual preference, and parenthood [NOW-NYS Chapter By-laws, 1976].
In 1974 NOW-New York State adopted by-laws defining the constituent element of its structure which consisted of members, member chapters, State Council, State Executive Committee, State Council Committees, State Task Forces, and the State Convention. The New York Chapter is overseen by the Executive Committee, made up of bi-annually elected officers who are composed of the President, Executive Vice-President, Secretary, Treasurer, and three members whose portfolio was to be determined [NOW-NYS Bylaws, adopted November 1974]. The revised 1976 by-laws defined the responsibilities of the three additional Executive Committee members and created two new positions: Vice-President of Membership, Vice-President for Legislation, Financial Vice-President, Vice-President of Public Information, and the Chairperson of the State Council. The Executive Committee forms the decision-making body at State Council meetings. The State Council is made up of two delegates from each local Chapter of the New York State Chapter, the Executive Committee Officers, and State Task Force heads. The State Council meets at least three times a year in Albany. The Albany Area Chapter was formed in January 1972, and subsequently became the central office for New York State. Bylaw changes are usually made at yealy National Conventions.
The State Convention is the general membership assembly of New York, responsible for formulation of general policy and program priorities. State Task Forces are approved and appointed by the Executive Committee. [NOW-NYS Chapter By-laws, 1976].
NOW-New York State Presidents
Eileen Kelly, 1974-1977
Zelle Andrews, 1977-1979
Sheila Molnar Feiger, 1979-1982
Theresa Bergen, 1982-1984
Noreen Connell, 1984-1988
Marilyn Fitterman, 1988-1992
Sharon Fawly, 1992-1996
Lois Shapiro Canter, 1996-2000
Kathryn Lake Mazierski, 2000-2004
Marcia Pappas, 2004- Sonia Ossorio, 2005 elected president of NOW-NYC, current president of NOW-NYS.
Scope and Contents
Includes State Council Meetings, Subject Files,Issues Files, Lobbyists' Files, Mailing Lists, Chapter Newsletters, Feminist Publications, and Correspondence. Conspicuously absent from the records are files from the early years of the organization. NOW-NYS has concentrated on educational and political activities both for and on behalf of women and women's rights.
The activities of the New York Chapter include, but are not limited to, such areas as lobbying at the State Capitol; monitoring the State Education Department to insure compliance with Title IX which forbids sex discrimination in schools; working in the area of domestic violence and battered women; monitoring the Division of Human Rights to determine whether women are fairly represented in employment discrimination complaints; working to preserve historic sites which have significance to women; helping women enter the work force for the first time; and lobbying for lesbian and reproductive rights.
NOW-NYS consistently shows concerns about the education system. Concerns include equality, sexism, discrimination in textbooks, programs such as Project Move or Project Voice (1981) and the displaced homemaker's programs of the later 1980s.It appears that the educational focus expanded from white collar to blue collar issues in the 1980s. The organization has a two-pronged education plan: to inform its members, and other women and men, about women's issues and rights through both educational and political avenues; and to prepare women to exercise those rights through job training programs.
Womens's rights, in the areas of health care, marriage, divorce, child custody, reproduction, and domestic relations are topics of concerns for NOW-NYS. In the area of employment, the organization has pursued job discrimination, sex discrimination, and pay inequalities. In various years NOW-NYS has tackled social issues including women against women, toys and toymakers, television portrayals of women, prostitution, lesbian and gay rights, pornography, sexual assault and battering, and divorce.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized as follows:
Series 1: State Council Meeting Files, 1974-2011
Series 2: Subject Files, 1968-1988
Series 3: Issues Files, 1961-2011
Series 4: Lobbyist Files, 1974-2011
Series 5: Mailing Lists, 1982-1984
Series 6: Chapter Newsletter File, 1971-2008
Series 7: Feminist Publications Collection, 1970-2008
Series 8: Correspondence, 1975-2010
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by NOW-NYS in 1987. Additional accessions were received from the Arthur and Elizabeth Schlesinger Library on the History of Women in America in 1996, 1999, and 2004. Additional accessions were received from NOW-NYS in 2005, 2009, and 2014.
Access
Access to membership and mailing lists in Series 5 is restricted. All other series are unrestricted. Consult a staff member for further details.
Women; Human Sexuality and Gender Identity; Athletics and Sports; Birth control--New York (State); Abortion services--Law and legislation--New York (State); Equal rights amendments.; Womens rights--New York (State); Homosexuality--Law and legislation--New York (State); Lobbying--New York (State); National Organization for Women.
- State Council Meeting Files, 1974-2011; 1; 3.06 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  The State Council Meetings include meeting minutes, cassette recordings of some State Council meetings, memoranda, agendas, correspondence, bylaws, newsletters, and State Convention and State Executive Committee minutes. The State Council Meetings document the structure, function, and activities of the state and local chapters, issues of concern to NOW-NYS on subjects ranging from abortion to education, and provide insight into the running of this state-wide women's network.
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 4), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 4), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - NYS Council Minutes (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - NYS Council Minutes (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 5), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 5), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - NYS Council Minutes (3 of 5), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - NYS Council Minutes (4 of 5), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - NYS Council Minutes (5 of 5), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 4), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 4), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NYS Council Minutes (3 of 4), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - NYS Council Minutes (4 of 4), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - NYS Council Minutes (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - NYS State Council, Cazenovia (1 of 6), 1980 July 19-20 (Cassette 1)
  - NYS State Council, Cazenovia (2 of 6), 1980 July 19-20 (Cassette 2)
  - NYS State Council, Cazenovia (3 of 6), 1980 July 19-20 (Cassette 3)
  - NYS State Council, Cazenovia (4 of 6), 1980 July 19-20 (Cassette 4)
  - NYS State Council, Cazenovia (5 of 6), 1980 July 19-20 (Cassette 5)
  - NYS State Council, Cazenovia (6 of 6), 1980 July 19-20 (Cassette 6)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (1 of 6), 1980 September 13-14 (Cassette 7)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (2 of 6), 1980 September 13-14 (Cassette 8)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (3 of 6), 1980 September 13-14 (Cassette 9)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (4 of 6), 1980 September 13-14 (Cassette 10)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (5 of 6), 1980 September 13-14 (Cassette 11)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (6 of 6), 1980 September 13-14 (Cassette 12)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (1 of 7), 1980 November 8-9 (Cassette 13)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (2 of 7), 1980 November 8-9 (Cassette 14)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (3 of 7), 1980 November 8-9 (Cassette 15)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (4 of 7), 1980 November 8-9 (Cassette 16)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (5 of 7), 1980 November 8-9 (Cassette 17)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (6 of 7), 1980 November 8-9 (Cassette 18)
  - NYS State Council, Albany (7 of 7), 1980 November 8-9 (Cassette 19)
  - NYS state Council Meeting, Continuation of Sunday Session, 1980 (Cassette 20)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 January 10-11 (Cassette 21)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 January 10-11 (Cassette 22)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 January 10-11 (Cassette 23)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 March 14-15 (Cassette 24)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 March 14-15 (Cassette 25)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 March 14-15 (Cassette 26)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 March 14-15 (Cassette 27)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 March 14-15 (Cassette 28)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 May 3 (Cassette 29)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 May 3 (Cassette 30)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 May 3 (Cassette 31)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 May 3 (Cassette 32)
  - NYS State Council, 1981 May 3 (Cassette 33)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 3), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - NYS Council Minutes (3 of 3), 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - NYS Council Minutes (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - NYS Council Minutes (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 3), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 3), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - NYS Council Minutes (3 of 3), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Calendar - Appointment Book, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Calendar - Appointment Book, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Calendar - Wall Hanging, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 4), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 4), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - NYS Council Minutes (3 of 4), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - NYS Council Minutes (4 of 4), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NYS Council Minutes (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - NYS Council Minutes (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Calendar - At-a-Glance, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Calendar - Marcia Pappas, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - NYS Council Minutes, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NYS State Council, SJ Speech, Sat.; Sunday Session, Undated (Cassette 34)
- Subject Files, 1965-2011; 2; 22.17 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  The Subject Files of the New York State Chapter of the National Organization for Women include internal and external correspondence, legal materials, memoranda, clippings, news releases, mailings, pamphlets, booklets, minutes, agendas, financial reports, by-laws, and more. The Subject Files document the structure, function, and activities of the state and local chapters. Present are issues of concern to NOW-NYS on subjects including, but not limited to, abortion and reproductive rights, battered women and domestic violence, children, politics, education (including educational opportunities for women, sexual discrimination), racism, lesbian and gay rights, job training, the Equal Rights Amendment and employment.
  - 20th Anniversary Show, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 21st Anniversary Conference Tape Program, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A 30 Year Celebration- Then and NOW, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 40 Years of Progress- Calendar, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1990 Elect The Team for Mow (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1998 National Board Survey (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 2000 Election Strategies, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 2000 Good Reasons to March (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 2004 Ballot- NOW- New York State Officers (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The ABCs of Women Issues, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Abortion, 1975; 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Abortion Rights Action- National Vigil for Women's Lives, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Abortion Rights Activist Alert, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Access, Privacy, Health, Freedom, Equality- We want Reproductive Justice NOW- Brochure, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Accomplishments of NOW New York State President and State Office, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Action Alert Network, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Action Alerts - July, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Action Reports, 1989; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Action- Team Network, 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - AD Book, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Addendum to Contract with Charitable Organizations, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - ADR Program Notice, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Advertising, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Affirmative Action, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Affirmative Action: Guidelines for Chapter, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Albany Area Chapter, 1972-1975; 2002-2004; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Albany Central Hotel, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Albany Office, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Alexandria Women's Health Clinic, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Alice Doesnt- Women's Strike, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Alice Paul Centennial Foundation, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Alliance for Women's Health Meeting- March 23, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - American Association of University Women, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - American Family Celebration, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Amicus Brief: Clubs, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Amicus Brief: Executive Order 50-AA, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Amicus Brief - Liberta- Marital Rape Exemption, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Amicus Brief- Marital Records, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Amicus Brief: New York State v. Emick (Wife Battering), 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Amicus Brief: Upper Hudson Valley Planned Parenthood of New York State Dept. of Health, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Amicus Brief: U.S. Power Squadrons, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Amsterdam Custody Case, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Analysis by Coalition for Family Justice of Deficiencies in the February, 2006 New York State Matrimonial Commission Report to the Chief Judge, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Analysis of Family Valence Option: Possible Areas of Comment Proposed Federal Regulations, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Ann Cowley Updates, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Annual Chapter Reports (1 of 2), 1987-1989; 1990- 1992; 1995-2003 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Annual Chapter Reports (2 of 2), 1987-1989; 1990-1992; 1995-2003 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Annual Convention- 10th Anniversary, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Annual Convention NOW- New York State, 1975-1984; 1998; 2001-2002; 2011 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Annual Membership Meeting Speech, Undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Annual NOW Political Debate, Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Anti NOW Campaigns, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Anti Poverty Information, Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Anti Trafficking Campaign- End the Business of Human Trafficking, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Appointments Coalition (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Appointments Coalition (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Arkansas NOW, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Articles for NOW Newspaper, Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Articles of Incorporation, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Assault on Women's Rights- October 15, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Assembly Judiciary Committee Child Custody Meditation Legislation Analysis of Hearing Testimony, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Assertiveness Training - June 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Adult Committee Report, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Association Compensation Survey, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Automation, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Background Information on Regional Proposal, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Balance Sheets, 1987; 1997; 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Balancing Work and the Family, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ballot for Electing Central New York Officers and Directors, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Baltimore NOW Clothesline Project, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bank Statements, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Bank Statements- Security Trust, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Barbara Lee Family Foundation, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Battered Mothers Conference - Sixth Conference - January 9-11, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Battered Women, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Battered Women, Abused Children, and Child Custody: A National Crisis, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Battered Women- Hospital Follow Ups, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Be a Media Activist, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Become a NOW- New York State Intern, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Behind The Labels: Garment Workers and U.S. Saipan, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Beth Edmonds, Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Beyond Empowerment - Living and Serving in a Sexist World- October 25, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - B.H.C.F. Chapter, 1987; 1990; Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Blending Humor and Controversy: American Cartoonist Comments on Reproductive Health, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Board Meeting- Notes, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Board Structure Committee, Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - The Bonus for Building Real Opportunities for Poor Families, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Borough President Ruth Messenger, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Brochures, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Bronx Chapter, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Brooklyn Chapter, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Brooklyn Chapter Lobby Day Recap, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Brunch- Liz Hertzman- June 13, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Budget (1 of 2), 1977-1987; 1989 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Budget (2 of 2), 1977-1987; 1989 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Budget Crisis, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Budget, Dues and Forms, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Budget and Legislative Priorities, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Budget Priorities, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Budget- Treasurers Report, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Budget Worksheet, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Bus to Washington, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Buffalo Chapter, 1979-1982; 1984 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Buttons, Undated
  - Bylaw Revisions, 1989-1989 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Bylaws, 1967-2010; Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Bylaws- California NOW, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Calendar of Events- Brooklyn, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Calendars, 2001; 2005; 1995-1996; 1999 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - California NOW, 1987-1988; 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - California NOW PAC Lottery, Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Campus Action Network Manual, Undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Campus Contacts, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Campus Organizing, Undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Candidate Declaration- NOW Buffalo and Niagara Chapter Officers, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Candidate Platforms, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Candidate Questioners, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Candidate Speeches, 1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Candidates For NOW- New York City 2002 Elections (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Candlelight Vigil- Shannon Lowney and Leanne Nicols, January 18, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Capital District- Gay and Lesbian Community Council - 2004 Annual Awards Dinner - October 27, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Capital District- Gay and Lesbian Community Council - 2007 Annual Awards Dinner (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Caregiving Testimony, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Catholic Charities of the Diocese of Albany vs. Gregory v. Serio, Undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Cecile C. Weich - Attorney and Lecturer, 1989; Undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Celebrating Staten Island's Professional Women - March 28, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - A Celebration of Black Women and Sisterhood, Undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Center for the Women of New York - 21st Annual Dinner - September 25, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Central New York Chapter, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Central New York Chapter (1 of 2), 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Central New York Chapter (2 of 2), 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Centralized Due Collection, 1979; 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Chair of Media Optional, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chapter Abroad- Military, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chapter Applications, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Chapter Building, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Chapter Contact Information, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Chapter Development, 1980; 1984; 1989; Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chapter Development- Going Down for the Third Time, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Chapter Developing Report- Planning Your State Conference/Council Meeting, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Chapter Information (1 of 2), 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)